Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- News Clippings, 1980-2013; 6; 2.8 cubic ft.
  - News Clippings, 2007 febuary-2007 April (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April-2007 September (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 2007 September-2008 January (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 2008 Febuary-2008 April (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 2008 April-2008 July (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 2008 July-2008 September (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 2008 September-2009 January (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 2009-January-2009 April (Box 3 (6-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 2009 May-2009 July (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 2009 July-2010 January (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 2010 January-2010 April (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 2010 May-2010 July (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 2010 July-2010 September (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 2010 October-2011 January (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 2011 January-2011 April (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 2011 May-2011 July (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 2011 September-2012 January (Box 4 (6-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 2012 January-2012 April
  - News Clippings, 2012 March-2012 July
  - News Clippings, 2012 July-2012 September
  - News Clippings, 2012 September-2013 January
- CSEA Communications, 1971-2015; 7; 1.8 cubic ft.
  This series includes press releases, weekly summaries, talking points, and speeches. Press releases, though incomplete, cover a broad range of topics from key issues to notification of meetings. The press releases are produced by CSEA and distributed in a paper format and posted on the CSEA website. The weekly summaries, also known as "Hot Sheets," are summary memos outlining the activities of the various CSEA departments for that week. They were distributed internally and offer a glimpse into the week to week work undertaken by the CSEA. The statements/speeches were made by CSEA leadership and officers regarding the union's position on key issues.
  - Press Releases, 1971 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 2)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1976-1977; 1979-1984; 1986 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1981 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 11)
  - Testimony, 1983 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 12)
  - Memoranda, 1984; 1988 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 14)
  - News Conference, 1984 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1990 January-1991 June (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1990 August-1990 December (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1991 January-1991 June (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1991 July-1991 December (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 25)
  - "Hot Sheets" - Weekly Summaries, 1993 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 27)
  - "Hot Sheets" - Weekly Summaries, 1994 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1995 January-1995 February (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1995 March-1995 December (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 30)
  - "Hot Sheets" - Weekly Summaries, 1995 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 31)
  - Transcript, 1996 January 19 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 32)
  - Talking Points, 1996 April 10 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1996 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 34)
  - "Hot Sheets" - Weekly Summaries, 1996 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1997 January-1997 April (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 36)
  - Press Releases, 1997 May-1997 December (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 37)
  - "Hot Sheets" - Weekly Summaries, 1997 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 38)
  - Statements, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1998 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1999 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 2000 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 2001 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 44)
  - CSEA Newsletter Kit, 2002 (Box 1 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 2003 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 2004 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 2005 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 2006 January-2006 May (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 2006 June-2006 December (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 2007 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 2008 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 8)
  - News Clips, 2009 May-2009 July (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 9)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2009 July (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 2009 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 11)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2010 March (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 2010 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 13)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2011 January (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 14)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2011 May (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 15)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2011 July (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 16)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2011 November (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 2011 (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 18)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 January (Box 2 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 19)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 April (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 1)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 July (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 2)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 September (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 3)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 November (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 2012 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 5)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2012 April (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 6)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2013 March 1 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 7)
  - Communications: Interim Report to the Board of Directors, 2013 May (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 8)
  - Communications: Report to the Board of Directors, 2013 July (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 9)
  - Executive Budget Proposal; Talking Points, 2013 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 2013 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 2014 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 2015 (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 13)
  - 20 Years of "The Public Sector" Your Story in Progress, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 14)
  - Confronting New Challenges; Joseph E. McDermott, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 15)
  - Local/Unit Website Guidebook, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 17)
  - Communication Guide, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 18)
  - Talking Points, Undated (Box 3 (7-CSEA Communications), Folder 19)
- Audio Visual, 1960-2013; 8; 21.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetical by format and then chronologically within each format.
  The Audio Visual series includes DVDs, CDs, VHS tapes, Beta tapes, DVDPros, and cassettes. The collection contains commercials, videos of guest speakers, such as Bill and Hillary Clinton, marches, speeches, conventions, and protests.
  - CSEA ADM - CSEA and Election "92", 1992 (1-inch type c 1)
  - Heart of New York, 1996 September 24 (1-inch type c 2)
  - CSEA Mental Health and Community Access, 2001 February 21 (1-inch type c 3)
  - CSEA: President Carter (1 of 3), 1980 October 1 (Beta 1)
  - CSEA: President Carter (2 of 3), 1980 October 1 (Beta 2)
  - CSEA: President Carter (3 of 3), 1980 October 1 (Beta 3)
  - CSEA Move, 1985 (Beta 4)
  - CSEA: Labor Day Parade (NYC), 1987 September 7 (Beta 5)
  - Labor Day T.V.: "Where Would We Be Without Them?", 1991 February 5 (Beta 6)
  - CSEA: "Keep Public Services Public" (Without Dinkins Signs) - 93 Convention Video, 1993 September (Beta 7)
  - CSEA: "In Touch With You", 1994 September 28 (Beta 8)
  - CSEA: "In Touch With You", 1995 October (Beta 9)
  - CSEA: Convention, 1998 October 8 (Beta 10)
  - CSEA: Convention, 1998 October 9 (Beta 11)
  - CSEA: 20,000 Marched - Unedited Parade Footage, Undated (Beta 12)
  - Bill Clinton at CSEA - NYC, 1992 September 24 (Beta 1)
  - Bill Clinton at CSEA - Convention, 1992 (Beta 2)
  - CSEA: Bill Clinton: New York State Electoral College Voting (1 of 2), 1992 (Beta 3)
  - CSEA: Bill Clinton: New York State Electoral College Voting (2 of 2), 1992 (Beta 4)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 3, 2W), 1993 September 29-1993 September 30 (Beta 5)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 1W, 1RA), 1993 September 29 (Beta 6)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 1RA, 1RB/3), 1993 September 29 (Beta 7)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 3), 1993 September 29 (Beta 8)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 2R, 4W), 1993 Septembr 30 (Beta 9)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 4R), 1993 September 30 (Beta 10)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 4W, 4R), 1993 September 30 (Beta 11)
  - CSEA: Recruitment Video (Scenes 2W), 1993 September 30 (Beta 12)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (1 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 13)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (2 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 14)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (3 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 15)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (4 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 16)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (5 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 17)
  - Commercial Drivers License: Alcohol and Drug Seminar (6 of 6), 1994 November 19 (Beta 18)
  - CSEA: Danny Donohue at State Fair (1 of 3), 1994 (Beta 19)
  - CSEA: Danny Donohue at State Fair (2 of 3), 1994 (Beta 20)
  - CSEA: Danny Donohue at State Fair (3 of 3), 1994 (Beta 21)
  - CSEA: Gabriel Thwats, 1994 (Beta 22)
  - CSEA: Tom Edwards, 1994 (Beta 23)
  - CSEA Rally, 1995 March 27 (Beta 24)
  - CSEA Rally 2, 1995 March 27 (Beta 25)
  - Gerry and Danny at the Capitol, 1995 June 14 (Beta 26)
  - AFSCME: B-Roll Pull Reels #2, 1996 (Beta 27)
  - CSEA 1: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 28)
  - CSEA 2: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 29)
  - CSEA 3: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 30)
  - CSEA 4: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 32)
  - CSEA 5: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 33)
  - CSEA 6: Joe McDermott, 1997 August (Beta 34)
  - "The AFSCME Advantage", 1998 October 1 (Beta 35)
  - "1998 Convention Video" (Beta 36)
  - Alex Beaucharnp, 1998 (Beta 37)
  - Belinda Auspelineyer, 1998 (Beta 38)
  - Cathy Duna, 1998 (Beta 39)
  - George Paye, 1998 (Beta 40)
  - Ice Storm, 1998 (Beta 41)
  - Mary Sullivan, 1998 (Beta 42)
  - R. Minkler, 1998 (Beta 43)
  - S. Lohmeyer, 1998 (Beta 44)
  - CSEA Rally: Brooklyn Bridge, Lucy AFSCME, and Interviews (1 of 2), 1999 September 28 (Beta 45)
  - CSEA Rally: Brooklyn Bridge, Lucy AFSCME, and Interviews (2 of 2), 1999 September 28 (Beta 46)
  - State of the State Rally (1 of 2), 2000 January 5 (Beta 47)
  - State of the State Rally (2 of 2), 2000 January 5 (Beta 48)
  - Hilary Clinton/Long Beach, 2000 August 1 (Beta 49)
  - "Friends", 2000 September 8 (Beta 50)
  - "That's Me" - Fall 2000 Campaign T.V. Spots, 2000 September 8 (Beta 51)
  - CSEA Conference Close, 2000 September 19 (Beta 52)
  - We Got the Power', 2000 September 21 (Beta 53)
  - AFSCME Lobby Day: Albany, NY (1 of 5), 2001 April 3 (Beta 54)
  - AFSCME Lobby Day: Albany, NY (2 of 5), 2001 April 3 (Beta 55)
  - AFSCME Lobby Day: Albany, NY (3 of 5), 2001 April 3 (Beta 56)
  - AFSCME Lobby Day: Albany, NY (4 of 5), 2001 April 3 (Beta 57)
  - AFSCME Lobby Day: Albany, NY (5 of 5), 2001 April 3 (Beta 58)
  - CSEA: Parade - Rochester, NY (1 of 2), 2001 September 3 (Beta 59)
  - CSEA: Parade - Rochester, NY (2 of 2), 2001 September 3 (Beta 60)
  - New York City Labor Day Parade (1 of 2), 2001 September 8 (Beta 61)
  - New York City Labor Day Parade (2 of 2), 2001 September 8 (Beta 62)
  - CSEA: Memorial March- Albany, NY (1 of 2), 2001 September 22 (Beta 63)
  - CSEA: Memorial March- Albany, NY (2 of 2), 2001 September 22 (Beta 64)
  - CSEA: Buffalo (1 of 2), 2001 September (Beta 65)
  - CSEA: Buffalo (2 of 2), 2001 September (Beta 66)
  - CSEA: Hempsted, 2001 October 10 (Beta 67)
  - CSEA: Nowak - 4:30 Spots, 2001 (Beta 68)
  - Oswego, 2001 (Beta 69)
  - Pledge of Allegiance/Star Spangled Banner, 2002 August 30 (Beta 70)
  - CSEA Delegates Assembly - 9/11 First Anniv. Central Park Vigil (1 of 2), 2002 September 11 (Beta 71)
  - CSEA Delegates Assembly - 9/11 First Anniv. Central Park Vigil (2 of 2), 2002 September 11 (Beta 72)
  - CSEA 2002 Convention Video, 2002 October 2 (Beta 73)
  - CSEA Victory in Ellenville (1 of 2), 2002 (Beta 74)
  - CSEA Victory in Ellenville (2 of 2), 2002 (Beta 75)
  - Joe McDermott (1 of 3), 2003 September 9 (Beta 76)
  - Joe McDermott (2 of 3), 2003 September 9 (Beta 77)
  - Joe McDermott (3 of 3), 2003 September 9 (Beta 78)
  - CSEA: Fall Tour Walmart and Weschester Conty, 2003 September 10 (Beta 79)
  - CSEA: Oswego, 2003 September 15 (Beta 80)
  - CSEA Annual Conference Video Presentation: "10 videos Total", 2003 (Beta 81)
  - CSEA Annual Conference Video Presentation: "AFSCME 25th", 2003 (Beta 82)
  - CSEA Annual Conference Video Presentation: "Bruno & Silver, 2003 (Beta 83)
  - CSEA- LEAD: Mary Sullivan, 2004 March 29 (Beta 84)
  - CSEA -LEAD: Danny, George, Kathy, Diane, 2004 March30 (Beta 85)
  - CSEA Hemstead 'B" Roll, 2003 September 17 (Beta 86)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (1 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 87)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (2 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 88)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (3 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 89)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (4 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 90)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (5 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 91)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (6 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 92)
  - CSEA Safety and Health Conference: Lake Placid, NY (7 of 7), 2006 April 27-2006 April 30 (Beta 93)
  - CSEA 2006:" The Star Spangled Banner," "Remebring, John J. Kelly J.r.," Leading the Fight For Worker Saftey" (Beta 94)
  - "CSEA 2006 Vignettes" (Beta 95)
  - CSEA: E. Kuiber, Undated (Beta 96)
  - CSEA: Kathy Bogarski, Undated (Beta 97)
  - CSEA: Linda Manusco, Undated (Beta 98)
  - CSEA: Mauor and Bus Garage, Undated (Beta 99)
  - CSEA: Sherrill Phillips, Undated (Beta 100)
  - CSEA: Sign Sharp, Undated (Beta 101)
  - Too Rapid, Too Radical: The Cost of Abandoning The Mentally Ill, Undated (Beta 102)
  - This is CSEA, 1969; 1970; 1974 (Cassette 1)
  - Wemdle Pension Broadcast, 1975 (Cassette 2)
  - Slide Show (1 of 3), 1970s (Cassette 3)
  - Slide Show (2 of 3), 1970s (Cassette 4)
  - Slide Show (3 of 3), 1970s (Cassette 5)
  - AFSCME Does Lattimer Stack, 1981 Janaury 10 (Cassette 6)
  - CSEA; 1981 Slide Show (Cassette 7)
  - Long Island Growing, 1984 October 5 (Cassette 8)
  - CSEA: Slide Show, 1984 May (Cassette 9)
  - Comp Worth News Conference, 1985 November 7 (Cassette 10)
  - NYS CWEP - 3 spots, 1985 June (Cassette 11)
  - McGowan- Asbestos Abatement Act - News Conference, 1986 March 11 (Cassette 12)
  - McGowan- Arvis, 1986 April 17 (Cassette 13)
  - Strikers & McGowan - Peter Winkels-Biz Agent and Rodney Hutchinson, 1986 May 7 (Cassette 14)
  - Riber- Orange County Survey, 1986 May 14 (Cassette 15)
  - CSEA Radio: Orange County NY, 1986 July 3 (Cassette 16)
  - CSEA: Sullivan County, 1986 July 21-1986 July 25 (Cassette 17)
  - CSEA: Orange County "Late Ballots", 1986 July 23-1986 July 25 (Cassette 18)
  - CSEA: Sullivan County - One Cut "Thank You", 1986 July 28 (Cassette 19)
  - CSEA: Orange County "Thank You", 1986 August 4 (Cassette 20)
  - Wm McGowan- Endrsemnt- D'Amato, 1986 August 27 (Cassette 21)
  - McGowan - Cuomo Endorsement, 1986 October 3 (Cassette 22)
  - Rockland County - 3 Spots, 1986 December (Cassette 23)
  - CSEA School Closing, 1986-1987 (Cassette 24)
  - CSEA: Rockland County Thank You - Vicki Burton and Pat Mashioli, 1987 January 28 (Cassette 25)
  - CSEA March on Kingston City Lab, 1987 March (Cassette 26)
  - Comp-worth Hartnett McGowan, 1987 April 7 (Cassette 27)
  - CSEA Radio; Binghamton Radio, 1987 June (Cassette 28)
  - CSEA, 1987 July (Cassette 29)
  - Bill McGowan and Pamela Newkirk, 1987 December 16 (Cassette 30)
  - CSEA: President McDermott- Contract Negotiations, 1989 November (Cassette 31)
  - CSEA: President McDermott "You've Had Enough", 1989 November (Cassette 32)
  - CSEA/AFSCME: Westchester Campaign, 1989 November (Cassette 33)
  - CSEA- Weschester Run-Off Election- Copy "A", 1989 December 27 (Cassette 34)
  - CSEA/AFSCME: Weschester Run-off, 1990 January (Cassette 35)
  - CSEA School Closing Spots, 1991 Janaury 4 (Cassette 36)
  - Snow Closing Spots #2, 1991 January 11 (Cassette 37)
  - Cuomo WG7, 1991 February 13 (Cassette 38)
  - WBLS - MH Cuts, 1991 February 26 (Cassette 39)
  - CSEA- "Snow Plow", 1991 February 13 (Cassette 40)
  - Off Center: Volume 1, 1991 (Cassette 41)
  - Off Center: Volume 2, 1991 (Cassette 42)
  - CSEA OMr, 1992 January 30 (Cassette 43)
  - CSEA Election, 1992 (Cassette 44)
  - CSEA: Privateers- Water Pharmacy, 1994 (Cassette 45)
  - Save America's Families Coalition - "Mother", 1995 September 6 (Cassette 46)
  - CSEA: All Antiprivatization Radio Spots, 1995 May 24 (Cassette 47)
  - CSEA: "Revised Monroe County Priv", 1996 August 26 (Cassette 48)
  - Prospering in America, 1997 March 4 (Cassette 49)
  - Prospering in America - NYC, 1997 May 13 (Cassette 50)
  - CSEA Convention, 1997 August 26 (Cassette 51)
  - Nowak Associates: February Contract, 1997 February (Cassette 52)
  - CSEA: 60 "Healthcare", 1998 March 12 (Cassette 53)
  - McCall Interview, 1998 May 5 (Cassette 54)
  - CSEA Capital Regular Tornado Radio, 1998 June 3 (Cassette 55)
  - Nowak Associates: :60 Contract Radio, 1998 August/1998 September (Cassette 56)
  - CSEA: 1999-2000 Theme (Cassette 57)
  - CSEA: Dev. Disabilities Radio #2, 1999 March 1 (Cassette 58)
  - CSEA: "Contract Outrage", 1999 April 27 (Cassette 59)
  - CSEA: Member Contract "Member Testimonials", 1999 June 3 (Cassette 60)
  - CSEA: Three Member Contract Radio, 1999 June 11 (Cassette 61)
  - CSEA: Nassau: 60 seconds (1 of 3), 1999 September 10 (Cassette 62)
  - CSEA: Nassau: 60 seconds (2 of 3), 1999 September 10 (Cassette 63)
  - CSEA: Nassau: 60 seconds (3 of 3), 1999 September 10 (Cassette 64)
  - CSEA: Contract, 1999 (Cassette 65)
  - CSEA: 1. Vote 2. School Closing 3. Theme, 1990s (Cassette 66)
  - Danny Donohue: Peoples Business, 1990s (Cassette 67)
  - COLA News Conference, 2000 May 9 (Cassette 68)
  - Star Spangled Banner: Cut 1 Vocal- Cut 2 No Vocal, 2000 August 22 (Cassette 69)
  - CSEA: Political Action, 2000 (Cassette 70)
  - Nowak/CSEA Interviews, 2001 February 7 (Cassette 71)
  - CSEA/Hanys "Healthcare", 2001 April 12 (Cassette 72)
  - Jerry Lefkowitz: Taylor Law, 2001 July 24 (Cassette 73)
  - William Blom, 2001 July 24 (Cassette 74)
  - Bob Laitimer, 2001 July 25 (Cassette 75)
  - Mary Langer, 2001 July 26 (Cassette 76)
  - CSEA: "Ulster County", 2001 August 28 (Cassette 77)
  - CSEA Members at Ground Zero, 2001 October 3 (Cassette 78)
  - CSEA: "Yonkers School Funding", 2001 Octobrt 16 (Cassette 79)
  - CSEA: :60 Radio "Buffalo Snow", 2002 January 11 (Cassette 80)
  - CSEA: :60 "Elenville Hospital, Ulster County", 2002 April 24 (Cassette 81)
  - CSEA: Long Island, 2002 May 31 (Cassette 82)
  - CSEA: :30 "Register/Vote" and "Vote", 2002 August 20 (Cassette 83)
  - CSEA: Bills Radio, 2002 September 15 (Cassette 84)
  - Tom Hartnett, 2002 December 19 (Cassette 85)
  - Rx Reform, 2002 December (Cassette 86)
  - CSEA - NYS Budget 2003, 2003 January; 2003 March (Cassette 87)
  - CSEA: James Roemer, 2003 April 2 (Cassette 88)
  - CSEA: Victor Costa, 2003 April 2 (Cassette 89)
  - CSEA: "Lewis County Recycling", 2003 June 24 (Cassette 90)
  - CSEA: Joe Dolan, 2003 July 09 (Cassette 91)
  - ASCME President Gerald McEntee and Secretary Treasurer William Lucy, 2003 July (Cassette 92)
  - Joe McDermott (1 of 2), 2003 September 9 (Cassette 93)
  - Joe McDermott (2 of 2), 2003 September 9 (Cassette 94)
  - CSEA: Nassau Health Care Corporation, 2004 January 14 (Cassette 95)
  - Danny Donohue, 2004 December 6 (Cassette 96)
  - Tom Quimby, 2004 December 7 (Cassette 97)
  - Liz Moore, 2005 April 16 (Cassette 98)
  - Mel osterman, 2005 May 3 (Cassette 99)
  - CSEA History Project: Chris Finan (1 of 2), 2006 January 25 (Cassette 100)
  - CSEA History Project: Chris Finan (2 of 2), 2006 January 25 (Cassette 101)
  - Harry Albright, 2005 July 13 (Cassette 102)
  - Al Demarco, 2006 March 7 (Cassette 103)
  - CSEE History Project: Paul Laetellani, 2006 March 7 (Cassette 104)
  - Danny Donohue: PESH, 2006 March 06 (Cassette 105)
  - Linda Angelo, 2006 March 15 (Cassette 106)
  - CSEA History Project: Dennis Hughes, 2006 June 21 (Cassette 107)
  - CSEA History Project: Dennis Walsh, 2006 June 21 (Cassette 108)
  - CSEA History Project: Marty Langer, 2006 June 22 (Cassette 109)
  - Joseph E. Persico (Author/Historian and Former Speech Writer for Rockefeller), 2006 July 18 (Cassette 110)
  - CSEA History Project: Jim Kelly, 2006 July 20 (Cassette 111)
  - Lonibery Wititm, 2007 January 29-30 (Cassette 112)
  - Jim Moore, 2007 April 24 (Cassette 113)
  - CSEA History Project: Michael Wilkins, 2007 August 19 (Cassette 114)
  - CSEA History Project: William Bronson, 2007 August 19 (Cassette 115)